Soar to New Heights of Adventure!
Barbie Mariposa is a animation, fantasy, family film directed by Conrad Helten.
Elina, heroine of the Fairytopia films tells her friend Bibble the story of
Flutterfield, a faraway kingdom populated by fairies with butterfly wings.
Henna, the evil butterfly fairy has poisoned the queen of
Flutterfield in an attempt to take over the kingdom.
Mariposa (voice), played by Chiara Zanni.
Willa / Coral / Flutterpixie (voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Rayna (voice), played by Kathleen Barr.
Rayla (voice), played by Erin Mathews.
Henna (voice), played by Nicole Oliver.
Prince Carlos (voice), played by Alessandro Juliani.
Barbie: Mariposa and Her Butterfly Fairy Friends, also known as Barbie: Mariposa, is a 2008
animated fantasy film directed by Conrad Helten and written by Elise Allen.
The tagline of the film is "The most beautiful thing you can be is yourself".
The film follows Mariposa (voiced by Chiara Zanni), a butterfly fairy on a Hero's Journey to save Queen
Marabella, and her kingdom, from the evil fairy Henna and the evil flying creatures – Skeezites.
The 12th installment in the Barbie film series, Barbie: Mariposa
is a spin-off of the Barbie: Fairytopia trilogy.
The film has a Spanish influence, with the titular
character's name being Spanish for 'butterfly'.
It is the first film in the series to not feature Kelly Sheridan's Barbie as the main role,
she instead reprises her role as the character Elina of the Fairytopia trilogy.
The film explores themes of magic, fairy, female
protagonist, butterfly, magic land.